#### **PROFILE**

Senior student with 3+ years of experience in full stack web development and a passion for problem-solving and learning new technologies. Previous experience in solving business problems at workplace, backed by strong communication skills and team-building mentality.

## **SKILLS**

React | Angular | HTML/CSS/JavaScript | Django ASP.NET | Ruby on Rails | NodeJS | Heroku | IIS MySQL/Postgresql/ MSSQL

# **EDUCATION**

# **Management Information Systems, B.S**

Minnesota State University Mankato

2015 - 2021 | Mankato, United States Certification in Software Development

CPGA: 3.07

Relevant Coursework: Software Engineering, Web Development, Software Quality Assurance & Testing, Database Applications, Systems Analysis & Design, Algorithms, Business Application Programming

## **LEADERSHIP**

### **Chief Executive Officer**

RiverBend Retailers

Provided strategic leadership to a student operated company that raised \$3000+ in profits to donate to Boys & Girls Club of Mankato

## **President**

Bangladesh Student Organization

Oversaw over 80 members of the organization, set up events and addressed their concerns regarding student life for international students

#### **VP Risk Management**

Inter-fraternity Council

Proactively ensure safety of all fraternity men on campus and manage all fraternity related risk incidents

## **Recruitment Chair**

Phi Kappa Psi

Meet students and potentially recruit them into Phi Kappa Psi fraternity

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Goodhue County**

Web Developer Intern

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020 | Red Wing, United States

- Created & deployed a web-based employee directory application that is currently being used by 250+ employees. Utilized Angular, ASP.NET Web API & IIS to replace a manual process.
- Implemented a comprehensive Social Media Policy for Goodhue County employees.
- Researched and analyzed Unified Endpoint Management solutions to enhance mobile device support for Goodhue County.

# **IT Solutions - Minnesota State University**

Technology Consultant

Jan 2019 - present | Mankato, United States

- Co-ordinate with vendors and other IT personnel to assist clients by providing expertise for a range of evolving technology products.
- Communicate with clients through email, telephone, and face to face.

## **PROJECTS**

## Project viewing available in portfolio link above

#### Todo Woo!

Personal Project

Application that lets a user create todo lists and track progress. (Django3)

# **Facial Recognition Application**

Personal Project

Application that can recognize faces from any image. (React, NodeJS, Express.js)

# **Goodhue County Employee Directory**

Internship Project

A web-based application deployed on Goodhue County's server for use by the Goodhue County Government Center, Sheriff's Office and Health & Human Services. (Angular, ASP.NET, IIS)

### **Extraterrestrial Life Evaluator- Earth Class ELE-**

Course Project

Autonomous Object Detecting & Following Robot operated with Raspberry Pi. (OpenCV, Python, Raspberry Pi3)